[English subtitles are available]
[My Journey to You]
[Episode 6]
In that case,
I'll check again.
A triangle mark
is used to leave a signal for allies.
It indicates a direction,
or where something is hidden.
Young Master Yuanzhi, sorry to keep you waiting.
What's in your hand?
Nothing special.
Let me see.
My brother never wears
such a golden and flashy accessory.
I just want to make Young Master Shangjue happy.
I don't know if something like this
will make my brother happy.
But if I don't send you to him
before dark,
he must be unhappy.
A union of fish and water in broad daylight!
That's not how you use that phrase.
What a beautiful couple!
I actually feel a little sad.
How should I put it?
It's like when I have to let my adult son go.
I think you're taking advantage of Sword Wielder.
What are you talking about?
He's my brother.
No matter how handsome he is, we can't be together.
My sister doesn't filter her words.
Don't mind her.
However,
she's a kind and nice person.
Miss Yun?
Eldest Young Miss has a good personality.
She's not arrogant
and is friendly towards others.
I also like listening to her talk.
Then you're doomed.
She'll annoy you to death if she sets her eyes on you.
It's a narrow road ahead. Follow me.
You must be wondering why there are so few people here.
Young Master Yuanzhi, you're amazing.
You can read people's hearts.
My brother likes peace.
Unless summoned,
the servants usually won't show up on their own.
I see.
Is Young Master Shangjue in the main hall?
Should I...
Why the hurry?
I'm new here.
I should greet Young Master Shangjue first.
I should honor
the basic etiquette.
Brother treats you so well.
He was worried that you would be neglected
in the Ladies' Hostel.
So he asked me to bring you here ahead of time.
I've never seen him
care so much for a girl.
He won't blame you
if you greet him a little later.
I'm grateful
for his kindness.
As such, I must further uphold my manners.
Why do you stop me?
I'm just curious.
What kind of charm do you have
to make my brother fall for you all of a sudden
and choose to marry you?
Pretty women can coax people
and fool people.
You're too kind, Young Master Yuanzhi.
Young Master Shangjue had already sent someone
to check on Yun Weishan and my background.
Their method of investigation
is different
from my method.
What is this?
Didn't you say I can read people's hearts?
Then, let me have a good read of yours.
You know martial arts?
I never said I can't.
Are you scared?
I'm not afraid of your investigation.
I'm just afraid of insects.
Leave the insect on your palm.
If you lie,
its venomous fangs
will pierce into your skin mercilessly.
In two hours,
your intestines and organs will rot.
Do you dare?
You dare not.
My feelings for Young Master Shangjue
are sincere
and genuine.
Even if you don't trust me,
you should trust
Young Master Shangjue's judgment.
You're right.
We have a long time ahead.
What is this impressive bug?
It can tell that someone's lying?
I lied to you.
It's just a medicinal ingredient.
In this world,
there's nothing that can really read people's hearts.
If there were,
it would have been destroyed long ago.
Shouldn't it be treasured?
How could it be destroyed?
People always say
they are chasing the truth.
But they are always running away from it.
People always say they despise secrets.
But everyone has secrets.
Even the abyss has a bottom,
but the human heart will always be unpredictable.
The human heart
is the most
vulnerable thing in the world.
Can I go see Young Master Shangjue now?
My brother doesn't meet guests at night.
Let me take you to the guest room first.
The servants will send the dinner
to your room later.
Thank you, Young Master Yuanzhi.
♫The memories you saw in your dream♫
♫Shone bright♫
♫In the rain♫
♫I set time into a chess game♫
♫Waiting for you♫
♫Every encounter is good luck♫
♫Every farewell is a regret♫
♫Fate is waiting to be written by the blade♫
♫The traces you left in the dream♫
♫It's like a riddle♫
♫There's no answer♫
♫I sewed winter clothes with memories♫
♫Every needle♫
♫Reminds me of you♫
♫Suddenly I forget the world♫
♫I hold your hand and worry about your lack of clothing♫
♫Without regret, the fallen do not give up on the world♫
♫I cross mountains and rivers to run towards you♫
♫To find you♫
♫And embrace your heart♫
♫I don't care about their reminder♫
♫I grip tightly to the blade♫
♫Let this sharp blade be the brush♫
♫To carve in my heart♫
♫You and me♫
♫A world only for us♫
You...
What are you doing?
Young Master Yuanzhi.
My concealed weapon pouch is missing.
What does that have to do with me?
Of course it does.
Search carefully.
Gong Yuanzhi.
This is against the rules.
Don't be guilty
if you didn't do it.
Otherwise,
you're suspicious.
I'm not suspicious.
But I have dignity.
Young Master Shangjue.
Brother.
What happened?
Young Master Yuanzhi lost his concealed weapon pouch
and wanted to search my room.
You...
Brother.
When I went to pick up Shangguan Qian,
the concealed weapon pouch was still on my waist.
But now it's gone.
Back at the Ladies' Hostel's courtyard,
she suddenly fell down
and held my waist for support.
I didn't react back then.
Now that I think about it,
she must have stolen my pouch
at that moment.
Why would I steal your concealed weapon pouch?
I don't even know how to use it.
Brother.
My concealed weapons
are different from the ones
sold by the Gong residence.
The structure and poison used are completely different.
If someone were to study them,
the power and secrets of these concealed weapons
would be exposed.
Miss Shangguan, have you been out of this room
since arriving here?
No.
The food was sent in.
The servants can testify.
Keep searching.
Yes.
Young Master Shangjue.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
We didn't find the concealed weapon pouch.
It must be on her.
Young Master Shangjue, did you really choose me
because you wanted to marry me?
I am the daughter
of an upright and righteous family.
Brother, trust me.
It's definitely on her.
Miss Shangguan,
I’m sorry.
Search her.
Found it.
This is not the one.
It shouldn't be a jade pendant in the pouch either.
It was her last time.
Enough.
Brother.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
Lord Sword Wielder found your concealed weapon pouch
by the river.
I went to the Zhi Lineage earlier.
The servants said you are here.
Lord Sword Wielder told me
to deliver it to you in person.
If you refer to Gong Ziyu as
Lord Sword Wielder in front of me again,
I'll cut off your tongue
and make medicine out of it.
Leave us.
Yes.
Brother Yuanzhi.
Apologize to Miss Shangguan.
Brother.
I...
Miss Shangguan,
I wronged you.
Sorry.
You don't have to return it to me.
This was originally my gift to you.
I've always wanted to ask
where this jade pendant
came from.
You don’t remember?
This jade pendant
belongs to you.
Of course I remember
about my jade pendant.
I'm asking about
where you got
this jade pendant.
Brother.
You know my concealed weapon pouch won't...
Won't easily fall off.
But as you saw,
you can't do anything about her.
Even if I trust you,
no one will believe you.
Brother,
you lost
that round just now.
I was careless.
Do you know what tool lions use to hunt?
Their sharp claws and fangs?
No.
Teamwork?
It's patience.
Patience?
When a lion is not completely certain,
it lies in the grass
and stays as still as a rock.
It never acts rashly.
Otherwise, once the cows are alarmed,
it will not be able to catch anything.
If a lion
were as reckless as you were just now,
it'd starve for the day.
What's worse,
this lion may be isolated by other lions
and eventually be exiled.
Understood.
Brother.
What do you understand?
Things are much more complicated than I thought.
And more interesting than I thought.
By the way,
go back and
check the concealed weapons in your pouch.
If I'm not mistaken,
someone must have tampered with them.
Brother,
you mean...
There is someone from Wufeng
still hiding in the Gong residence.
Young Master Ziyu.
You dropped something.
Young Master Yuanzhi.
Lord Sword Wielder found your
concealed weapon pouch by the river.
Sister Zishang gave me this pastry.
It's really delicious.
I'll give you this.
Can you show me your little butterfly?
♫Will I see you again?♫
No.
Father said
we are brothers.
Brothers
must give each other the best things.
♫The summer we spent together is a blur now♫
I don't want to be brothers with a bastard.
I'm not a bastard!
You are!
♫Night breezes tousled your gray hair♫
♫You looked at me in silence♫
Mother.
They said I...
They said I'm...
♫When you put your hands on my shoulders♫
How can a boy cry so easily?
♫All my fear and hesitation were gone♫
How many times have I told you?
Remember to go to the clinic
when you're injured.
♫Snow falls, my wounds would never close♫
I don't want to go to Zhi Lineage.
Gong Yuanzhi called me a bastard.
I don't want to play with him.
♫I've been adrift for too long but now I'm home♫
Mother!
Who made you cry?
Father will punish him severely.
Father, why is Mother ignoring me?
Well,
I can't help you with that.
Because your mother
is ignoring me too.
♫Yesterday fades like a distant mountain♫
♫Tears are the snow♫
♫On the top of the mountain♫
You don’t remember?
This jade pendant
belongs to you.
Of course I remember
♫You whisper loving words in my ear♫
about my jade pendant.
I'm asking about
where you got
♫Yet we have no choice but to part♫
this jade pendant.
Miss, aren't you cold here?
♫I hold the blade in my hand♫
I'll take you to a warm place.
Let go of me!
Help!
Go!
♫And slice through the night♫
Who are you?
♫Feelings are always so bland on paper♫
♫But writing it feels so bitter and intolerable♫
♫I mock people who are obsessed with love and hate♫
♫But only half my heart remains♫
♫Only I looked up when we crossed paths♫
♫Leaving a moment behind♫
Four years ago, during the Lantern Festival,
♫At the shore of the flow of time♫
I ran into thugs on the way.
Young Master Shangjue, you
♫I heard a door open♫
happened to pass by and rescued me.
♫The later the night, the warmer the heart♫
You dropped this
back then.
♫Yet the hug feels colder than the snow♫
I've always wanted to repay you for saving my life.
♫Why do we stand side by side?♫
You don't have to.
I was just dealing with people who were in my way.
I did not intentionally save you.
It was just a coincidence.
Don’t worry about it.
Even if you didn't intend to save me,
in my opinion,
you protected my dignity, which is most important to a lady.
As such, my heart already belongs to you.
In the past,
I dared not dream about it
due to the difference in our status.
I didn't expect
to be able to marry you now.
We're only engaged.
The Gong residence is huge.
Don't wander about.
Stay where you belong,
in the right place.
Don't take the wrong path.
I'll listen to you.
Miss Yun.
It's late. Why are you still up?
Aren't you still up too?
Are you not used to sleeping in a new place?
Shall I ask the servants
to prepare some soothing medicine for you?
Did I say something wrong?
You can't sleep either,
but you worry about getting soothing medicine for me instead.
Did I say something wrong?
No.
I just moved to a new place too.
They said I'm already a Sword Wielder.
So they moved me into my brother's old room.
Lord Sword Wielder.
These are the former young master's clothes.
The room
is filled with traces of his past.
The decoration hasn't changed either.
It's like
he never left.
It's almost winter.
It's cold at night.
But your face is full of sweat.
Did you have a nightmare?
Why aren't you wiping your sweat?
Looks like
you're used to being served.
Did others wipe your sweat for you in the past?
No.
Except my mother.
My mother
would wipe my sweat,
but she wouldn't wipe my tears.
Did you cry a lot
when you were young?
We all have things we're sad about.
But my mother told me
a man shouldn't cry.
So later,
I stopped crying.
I used to
often have nightmares too.
When I couldn't sleep,
my younger sister would sing for me.
♫The sun rises in the east and sets in the west♫
♫Our parents call us home for dinner♫
♫We grew up together♫
♫We never wake up from our sweet dreams♫
♫Spring brews life, and Winter brews coldness♫
♫You're always in my thoughts♫
♫Summer is long, and Autumn is brief♫
♫I hope we can reunite again♫
As long as I listened to her singing,
I stopped having nightmares.
You and your younger sister
must be very close.
You left Lixi Town
and came to the Gong residence.
She must miss you very much.
Thank you.
For what?
I didn't answer.
You didn't ask again.
Sometimes,
giving no answer
is also an answer.
I always wanted to return this to you,
but I didn't find the right time.
This ornament.
I saw you hang it on yourself every day.
It must be something you cherish.
Yes.
My father gave it to me.
My father used to be a businessman.
He had also seen all kinds of leather.
This fox fur
has a pure color
and a symmetrical pattern.
The fox fur is the finest.
Your father must have put
a lot of effort into finding it.
My father
had always been meticulous.
He had his intentions.
But
I'm young and shallow.
I've never understood them.
At the age of 30, people stand firm.
At the age of 40, people have no doubts.
Sword Wielder, you're still young.
How can you see everything clearly?
Why did you call me Sword Wielder again?
Didn't I ask you to call me Young Master Ziyu
in private?
Then
don't call me Miss Yun anymore.
Okay.
What should I call you?
Why don't you answer?
Sometimes,
giving no answer
is already an answer.
You're amazing.
All Gong Ziyu thinks about
is you.
But I'll still fail him.
You'll fail him.
You'll destroy his life
completely.
When there are rivers of blood in the Gong residence,
I really want to see
how Gong Ziyu will look at you.
When will Gong Ziyu go to the back hill?
Soon.
I'll try to ask.
Your task
is to draw a map of the Gong residence,
right?
For a long time,
only Gong, Shang, Jue, Zhi, and Yu have been known in the martial world.
I've never heard
of the back hill.
It's so mysterious.
I asked several servants,
but they said they didn't know.
If you can find out the situation of the back hill,
Hanya Si will be very happy.
I don't need you to tell me.
I'll definitely investigate it.
The back hill is an important place.
It's not easy to enter there.
I have a way to trail him.
How?
There are just several tracking methods
in the Wufeng.
Make inferences from traces.
Tail people in disguise.
Predict destinations.
Change shifts.
Yes.
There is another method.
Scent tracking.
But
scent tracking is the hardest one.
Why haven't I heard
people at the Chi level can do this?
There are many things you don't know about the Wufeng.
Fine.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Shouldn't you thank me too?
You're so bold.
Only risky moves
can bring people back from the brink.
Did you gain a lot?
It's enough.
Enough for what?
It's enough for me to survive half a month.
What about you?
I'm not worried about this.
What I'm worried about
is how we can go out
after half a month.
Are you telling me or not?
Everyone knows
the Trial of the Three Realms is dangerous.
You know something about it.
Why don't you tell me?
Are you still my Green Jade Guardian?
Lord Sword Wielder.
I've sworn
that I won't mention anything about the back hill.
Don't force me.
[Gong Residence, Back Hill]
Recently, there has been a lot of explosions in the Shang Lineage in the front hill.
At first, I thought people from the Wufeng stormed in.
Later it turned out
that Eldest Young Miss Gong ZiShang was doing research.
It was just a false alarm.
What research was she doing?
I don't know.
She seemed to
combine gunpowder and weapons.
Isn't it a hidden weapon
made by Young Master Yuanzhi before?
Interesting.
I'm going to the front hill.
Forget it.
You don't want to tell me.
I can't force you to do it.
You don't want to leave.
I can't break your legs.
When I leave,
remember to keep an eye on Gong Shangjue and Gong Yuanzhi.
Lord Sword Wielder.
Please be careful.
Don't act tough.
You...
You refused to tell me, but you look like you want to say something.
Why are you so annoying?
It was nothing.
After hearing what you said,
I'm more nervous.
Lord Sword Wielder.
What's this? It's so heavy.
Miss Yun is so thoughtful.
She's already packed your luggage.
I heard from Guardian Jin
that
you can leave the back hill only after completing the first trial.
The back hill is damp and cold.
Sister Zishang said
you've been afraid of cold since childhood.
So I brought some warm clothes.
There's also alcohol.
Unfortunately,
I'll go alone this time.
Some heartless people won't go with me.
It seems
that I can only drink alone.
This is not ordinary alcohol.
The back hill has a heavy miasma
and high humidity.
Miss Shangguan had cold in her body before.
A physician in the clinic gave her a prescription.
I made the medicinal alcohol according to it.
It can prevent cold and damp.
There're also some cakes.
I'm afraid you won't like the food in the back hill.
By the way,
I made a pouch.
The herbs inside are for repelling mosquitoes.
My hometown Lixi Town was built along a river.
There are many snakes, insects, mosquitoes, and ants there.
When I was a child,
my mother always asked me to carry it with me.
Here is the Gong residence.
No snake, insect, mosquito, and ant can get close to me.
It doesn't matter.
You've already made it.
I'll take it.
Look at you.
You just came to the Gong residence.
You prepared so many things.
You must be tired.
After my father passed away,
the situation in my family changed.
Many servants were dismissed.
I'm used to working.
It's nothing.
From now on,
you don't have to do these things.
Let others do them.
I should do these things.
After all, I was selected by you as...
I was selected by you as...
As what?
Sword Wielder, is there anything else you need?
What's wrong with your eyes?
When are you leaving?
Three days later. It's the eighth day of the first lunar month.
It's unsuitable to farm but suitable to go out on that day.
Let me go with you.
I can take care of you.
I'm afraid you can't.
The offspring of the Gong family who go for the trial
can only bring their personal Green Jade guardians.
Be careful, Sword Wielder.
What went wrong?
Tell me.
Why?
This is the room
of Eldest Young Miss who likes doing research?
The saltpeter produced too much smoke when burning.
The amount of charcoal and sulfur was obviously too much.
It burnt too fast,
so it was easy to expand.
Alright.
You don't need to clean here.
Yes, Eldest Young Miss.
I'll leave now.
Stop!
What did you say just now?
The saltpeter
produced too much smoke when burning.
The amount of charcoal and sulfur was obviously too much.
It burnt too fast,
so it was easy to expand.
What's your name?
Xiaohei.
Who do you work for? Why do you know these things?
My grandpa makes fireworks.
He's really good at it.
The fireworks made by my family were also set off in the capital city before.
Alright. Stay here.
To clean here?
Let's play together.
It's time to say goodbye.
Enough.
You two are heartless. Stop acting.
It's okay for you to blame Jin Fan.
Why
do you also blame me?
Sword Wielder.
Remember,
don't act tough.
Young Master Ziyu.
Let me go to the entrance to the back hill with you.
-No.
The back hill is an important place.
Outsiders are not allowed in.
Irrelevant people are not allowed to get in.
We don't know martial arts.
We don't have many things to do.
The back hill is dangerous and terrifying.
Let him go
and have an adventure.
Young Master Ziyu.
Take care.
Wait for me.
[Gong Residence, the Entrance to the Back Hill]
Jin Fan.
Did you practise handstands after breakfast again?
You look so pale.
Jin Fan.
Do you know something
about the Trial of the Three Realms?
You're so nervous.
Will Young Master Ziyu's life be in danger?
You're so annoying.
Even a mute is not as annoying as you. Say something.
Jin Fan.
I know you swore
that you won't mention anything about the back hill.
You don't have to say anything.
Just nod or shake your head.
It's not a violation of your vow.
Will his life be in danger
in the Trial of the Three Realms?
Do you know
what the first trial is?
Does it test his intelligence?
Does it test his martial art skills?
Does it test his zero-gravity martial art skills?
Does it test his internal skills?
Zishang.
Jin Fan.
I need you to do me a favor.
What is it?
Help me to go to the back hill.
Let me replace Jin Fan to protect Sword Wielder.
No way.
The back hill is an important place.
Outsiders are not allowed in.
Right?
Irrelevant people are not allowed to get in.
I'm not irrelevant.
I'm not an outsider.
I was selected by Lord Sword Wielder as his wife.
Although I haven't officially married Sword Wielder,
he's already my husband
in my heart.
Jin Fan.
You just said his life will be in danger in the Trial of the Three Realms.
If Young Master Ziyu dies in the trial,
I won't live.
But if he passes the trial,
he'll be the legitimate Lord Sword Wielder.
Is the wife of Sword Wielder
eligible to enter the back hill?
Dear, stop messing around.
Even though you're not an outsider, you don't know martial arts.
What can you do there?
Jin Fan knows martial arts.
He can protect Sword Wielder.
If you go...
What if I can defeat Jin Fan?
Why are there
many kinds of dishes today?
The food is hot.
You came just in time.
Were all these dishes
cooked by you?
Don't mind if they look bad.
They indeed look bad.
What is this?
It looks like
a pheasant.
I specially asked people from the kitchen to go up the mountain and hunt it.
I removed the skin and bones and fried them once before putting it in a pan.
The Shangguan family is distinguished in Dafu City.
You're Eldest Young Miss.
You know these?
My mother said
only women who can cook
can keep people.
Have a seat.
Brother Yuanzhi, why don't you eat after Young Master Shangjue?
My brother spoils me.
He always lets me eat delicious food first.
Although you're spoiled,
you should have good manners.
We're brothers.
There is no need to stand on ceremony.
I think
Lord Sword Wielder
is quite polite.
That's why he's not our brother.
What do you mean?
And he's not Sword Wielder.
Eat.
Young Master Shangjue, help yourself.
There's food in Brother Yuanzhi's bowl.
Don't call me
Brother Yuanzhi.
Only my elder brother can call me brother.
Aren't you polite?
Then call me Young Master Yuanzhi from now on.
After we get married,
you can call him brother.
My brother is a vegetarian.
He eats stew at most.
I'm afraid the dishes you cooked will be wasted.
That's why
Young Master Shangjue has a weak stomach and has no appetite.
You grew up with Young Master Shangjue.
He only eats one meal every day.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
I did wrong.
Please punish me.
Oh?
What did you do wrong?
It was my fault
for speculating about your thoughts.
What did you get?
You
only eat stew.
You don't eat whole chicken and fish.
I guess
it's because of their eyes.
My father once told me
that soldiers who fight on battlefields
seldom eat fish.
Because the eyes of fish
are the same
as the eyes of the dead.
All these years,
you've been risking your life for the Gong family.
You've seen many bloody scenes.
Actually,
you never said it,
but you still have hard feelings.
You know a lot.
Aren't you giving it to me?
Aren't you giving me
the soup you ladled into the bowl?
I want it too.
Let her ladle it.
[Yu]
A competition between gentle people
doesn't hurt each other.
This is the knife used by guardians.
It's a bit heavy
for girls.
It doesn't matter.
Brother.
Gong Ziyu has gone to the back hill.
There is nothing to worry about.
If he has self-awareness,
he should give up early.
If he doesn't have self-awareness,
let's remind him.
His shameful background.
Do you know where to start?
Miss Shangguan.
I want a bowl of sweet soup.
I wonder
if there is some in the kitchen?
Yes.
Lady Lan.
Lady Lan?
Isn't she dead?
Dead people can't speak,
but people who are alive can speak for her.
The personal servant who served Lady Lan when she was pregnant
must know more than us.
I won.
Jin Fan.
Although you battled with me with a knife,
all your moves are the moves for using swords.
I happen to know the sword technique you used.
Qingfeng Nine Moves Sword.
It's the Qingfeng Sect's secret top-class sword technique that hasn't been passed down.
The Qingfeng Sect has joined the Wufeng.
Tell me.
What's your identity in the Qingfeng Sect?